http://www.matadors.org/privacy-policy

Acknowledge
Matadors Community Credit Union may collect the following information from users of our website. To see how this information is used, click here to go to our privacy page. Information we may collect: IP address, browsing history, search history, products and services considered, geolocation data, and information about your interaction with our website, application or advertisement. If you complete an online form, we may also collect your name, e-mail address, physical address or phone number that you provide to us.
Tools & ResourcesBusinessAccount ServicesBorrowBank
Matadors Money Matters Blog
Holidays
MCCU Newsletter
Forms & Applications
Annual Report
Financial Calculators
Insurance Services
Teen Savers Checking
College Savings (UTMA)
Checking Accounts
Free Checking
Premium Checking
Fresh Start Checking
Checking Services
Debit Cards
Online Banking
Mobile Banking
Online Privacy Policy
Maintaining your online privacy and the security of your personal information is important to us.  This Online Privacy Notice is designed to inform you of our website and online information privacy practices, the types of information we collect, how the information is used, and to assure you that we maintain strict security procedures to protect your information.
In addition to our Online Privacy Policy, please be sure to view our other Privacy Policies:
Federal Privacy Policy
Important Privacy Choices for California Members
California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Rights
This Online Privacy Policy statement describes our privacy practices with respect to our website - www.matadors.org and our Online Banking Service, eBranch.
Surfing our Website and Using Online Banking (eBranch)
We use cookies to track usage of our website and to compile general statistics.
Our Online Banking service (eBranch) requires the use of cookies to keep track of your identity and other information pertinent to your internet banking session. Cookies are small pieces of information that a Web server can store on your browser so the system recognizes your actions during a session. When you end your session with eBranch (exit browser), all eBranch cookies are automatically removed. This means that a third party attempting to access these cookies directly from your computer hard drive would not be able to find them. The user name and password you enter to access eBranch is used to verify your identify before online access is granted.
Information we collect from you when you request information about the Credit Union’s products and services
We ask for your first and last name, address, e-mail address, home phone number and your work phone number when you request membership information from us. We ask this information for two reasons: 1) to deliver the information to you, 2) to follow up with you to make sure that you have received the information you previously requested and to help you with any questions you may have about the information we have sent to you.
Use of your E-mail address
When you sign up for Online Banking (eBranch), Bill Pay, and for membership, we ask for your e-mail address in order to periodically send you information about our products and services. We may also use your e-mail address to communicate important information about your account and the services associated with it.
E-mail addresses and other information for the “MCCU News” electronic newsletter function
For each visitor that signs up for MCCU e-news, we collect only the information that is requested on the list signup form. Required fields are denoted with an asterisk (*). Our web servers may collect the domain name or IP address of visitors to our web page(s). Unless otherwise stated on our web site, we collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail and information volunteered by you such as but not limited to list signup information and the signature card for your account(s). In our e-mail messages to you which are distributed through this list, we may have information from third party providers for products and services which may be advertised or promoted within messages we send to you from this e-mail list--the privacy policies of those third-party provider sites govern the method by which they collect and use such information.
Use of Web Site Information Collected
The information we collect may be used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base so that we can improve content, customize the content and/or layout of our e-mail messages or pages for each individual visitor, to notify you about updates to our web site and services, to provide you with the products and/or services for which you signed-up or registered, which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via e-mail, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. Upon request, we will provide you with the information (e.g., e-mail address, name, etc.) that we maintain about you.
Postal Address Collection and Use
If you supply us with your postal address online you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. If you supply us with your telephone number, you will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding your inquiry.
Cookies
We may use cookies to record session information, such as record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when you return to our site, and customize web page or e-mail message content based on your browser type or other information.
Do Not Track Signals
We do not use tracking information or pass this type of information to third parties. MCCU’s web server automatically recognizes only your IP address when you visit our site. It does not recognize your email address or other personal information.
Third-Party Links and partnered service providers
Matadors Community Credit Union does not control and cannot guarantee the relevance, timeliness and accuracy of the materials provided by the other websites, nor does Matadors Community Credit Union endorse their views, products or services. Each of these third party websites has a different privacy policy. For your own protection, we encourage you to familiarize yourself with each one.
Matadors Community Credit Union also partners with different service providers for services such as mortgage lending and student loans to provide you with services we would not otherwise be able to provide to you. These third party companies may collect information directly from you in order to provide you with the service you have requested. Please be advised that we hold our partners to strict confidentiality standards and prohibit them from sharing your information with any party other than Matadors Community Credit Union.
We reserve the right to change this policy in the future by posting notice at this site. Please contact us at 818-993-6328 or e-mail info@matadors.org if you have any questions regarding this privacy notice.
Go to main navigation
Helpful Links
Business Rates
Savings Rates
Loan Rates
Refer a Friend
Fee Schedules
Consumer Fee Schedule
Business Fee Schedule
See All | Contract AllHomeBank
Open an AccountSavings Accounts
Regular SavingsSavers PlusShare CertificatesHealth Savings AccountsRetirement AccountsSavings RatesSavings Calculators
Youth Accounts
Little SaversTeen SaversTeen Savers CheckingCollege Savings (UTMA)
Checking Accounts
Free CheckingPremium CheckingFresh Start CheckingChecking Services
Debit Cards
Online Banking
Mobile Banking
Online Bill Pay
Reorder Checks
Overdraft Protection
Automatic Deposit Options
Gold/Platinum MembershipCourtesy PaySenior Banking
MCCU Switch KitsBorrow
Auto Loans
New Auto LoansUsed Auto LoansAuto Loan RefinancingAuto Buying ServicesAutoland Car BuyingMechanical Breakdown InsuranceGAP Insurance
Loan CalculatorsRecreational LoansSolar LoansHome Energy LoansPersonal LoansCredit CardsMortgagesHome Equity Line of CreditShare & Certificate LoansStudent LoansAdvance Pay LoansSkip-a-PayLoan RatesAccount Services
eStatementsATMsShared BranchingWire TransfersAdditional ServicesBusiness Services
Business SavingsBusiness CheckingBusiness LoansBusiness Credit CardsMerchant ProcessingBusiness CalculatorsBusiness RatesTools & Resources
Matadors Money Matters BlogHolidaysMCCU NewsletterAnnual ReportEmploymentFinancial CalculatorsMembership PerksEstate Planning ServicesEmployer GroupsForms and ApplicationsInsurance Services
Auto/Home InsuranceLife InsuranceAD&D Insurance
